Guide to the Michael Bennett Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Michael Bennett papers
1950-1989
1973-1986
YCAL MSS 538
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
58.67
(69 boxes)
The papers document the musical theater career of Michael Bennett, spanning the dates 1950 to 1989 (with the bulk of the material spanning 1973 to 1986), and consisting of production files, correspondence, business papers, scripts, printed material, personal papers, audiovisual material, objects and photographs. The papers document the process of writing, choreographing, directing, and marketing Broadway musical productions such as Dreamgirls and A Chorus Line. The papers also document Bennett's personal life in the 1970s and 1980s.
Bennett, Michael, 1943-1987
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Robert Avian, 2003.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 52-55, 68-69 (audio and video tapes): Restricted Fragile Material. Access to original audio and video tapes is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Contact Access Services for further information.
Scope and Contents
The papers document the musical theatre career of Michael Bennett, spanning the dates 1950 to 1989 (with the bulk of the material spanning 1973 to 1986), and consisting of production files, correspondence, business papers, scripts, printed material, personal papers, audiovisual material, objects and photographs. The papers document the process of writing, choreographing, directing, and marketing Broadway musical productions such as Dreamgirls and A Chorus Line. The papers also document Bennett's personal life in the 1970s and 1980s.
Arrangement
Organized into three series: I. Production Files, Professional Papers, and Personal Papers, 1950-1987. II. Awards and Objects, 1970-1989. III. Audiovisual Material, 1966-circa 1986.
Michael Bennett, 1943-1987
American musical theater director and choreographer Michael Bennett was born Michael DiFiglia in Buffalo, New York in 1943. Bennett began his Broadway career as a dancer and later found success as a choreographer and director. Bennett won seven Tony Awards for his choreography and direction of Broadway shows, and was nominated for eleven more. Bennett is best known for his work on Promises, Promises, Dreamgirls, A Chorus Line, Ballroom, Company and Follies. Bennett died of AIDS-related lymphoma in 1987.
Choreographers -- New York (State) -- New York; Choreography -- New York (State) -- New York; Gay men and musicals; Musical theater -- Production and direction; Musical theater producers and directors; Musicals; Audiotapes; Audiovisual materials; Photographic prints; Scripts (documents); Videotapes; Musical theater producers and directors -- New York (State) -- New York; Choreographers -- New York (State) -- New York; LGBTQ resource; Bennett, Michael, 1943-1987
- Production Files, Professional Papers, and Personal Papers, 1950-1987; Series I; 38 linear feet (38 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Files are grouped together by production title, format, or topic, but otherwise are not arranged in any particular order.
  Scope and Contents
  Series I consists of production files for Broadway shows and other professional and personal papers. Production files pertain to the musicals and plays on which Bennett worked, and include scripts, financial and legal records, contracts, marketing material, photographs, newspaper clippings, playbills, and other related material. Professional papers include correspondence and other papers relating to Bennett's work on Broadway, and also to professional organizations and associations, studios and theatres, and labor relations. Personal papers contain personal correspondence, household maintenance files, financial papers, and diaries and daily calendars.
  - A Chorus Line, production files, circa 1977-1985; 38 (Box 1)
  - Professional and personal papers, circa 1975-1985; 10 folders (Box 1)
  - A Chorus Line, production files, circa 1976-1985; 25 (Box 2)
  - A Chorus Line, production files, circa 1977-1985; 34 (Box 3)
  - A Chorus Line, production files, circa 1978-1983; 53 (Box 4)
    Most files pertain to national and international tours of A Chorus Line.
  - A Chorus Line, production files, circa 1976-1985; 29 (Box 5)
  - A Chorus Line, production files, circa 1975-1982; 26 (Box 6)
  - A Chorus Line, production files, 1976-1983, undated; 16 (Box 7)
  - A Chorus Line, production files, 1978-1983; 14 (Box 8)
  - A Chorus Line, production files, 1977-1986; 18 (Box 9)
  - A Chorus Line, production and litigation files, circa 1975-1976; 19 (Box 10)
    Includes testimonies by Michael Bennett and James Lipton.
  - A Chorus Line, bound music score, undated
  - A Chorus Line, photographs, newspaper clippings, and "Dreamgirls Day" proclamation (Series I.), circa 1976-1986
  - Dreamgirls, production files, 1981-1985; 39 (Box 11)
  - Professional papers, 1976-1983; 12 (Box 12)
  - Dreamgirls, production files, 1980-1985; 19 (Box 12)
  - Dreamgirls, production files, circa 1980-1985; 42 (Box 13)
  - Dreamgirls, production files, circa 1980-1986; 14 (Box 14)
  - Dreamgirls, bound music score, 1984
  - Production files, circa 1974-1985; 29 (Box 15)
    Includes A Chorus Line, Big Dreams, Chess, Follies, God's Favorite, and Dreamgirls.
  - Company, bound music score, 1971
  - Follies, bound music score, 1971
  - Production files, 1977-1983; 31 (Box 16)
    Includes Big Dreams, Our Father, and Treva Silverman's script.
  - Production files, circa 1973-1985; 33 (Box 17)
    Includes Coco, Follies, Twigs, God's Favorite, Seesaw, A Chorus Line, A Joyful Noise, and Ballroom.
  - Personal papers, circa 1976-1983; 7 (Box 17)
  - Production files, circa 1980-1985; 21 (Box 18)
    Includes "Scandal" and Treva Silverman's script.
  - Personal financial papers, 1984-1985; 5 (Box 18)
  - Production files, 1979-1986; 13 (Box 19)
    Includes Love Me or Leave Me, The Superlative Horse, and Black River.
  - Production files and professional papers, 1978-1987; 29 (Box 20)
    Includes Bob Avian files, Treva Silverman's script, A Chorus Line, and Seesaw.
  - Personal papers, circa 1980; 8 folders (Box 20)
  - Playbills and production files, circa 1976-1984; 18 (Box 21)
    Includes scripts of A Chorus Line, Big Dreams, Smile, Ishtar, Firetown, Wenceslas Square, and Treva Silverman's script. Also inlcludes playbills for A Chorus Line.
  - Playbills, circa 1967-1985; 16 (Box 22)
    Includes playbills for A Chorus Line, Ballroom, and the Tony Awards ceremony.
  - Professional papers, circa 1978-1986; 47 (Box 23)
    Includes files on the building at 890 Broadway, labor relations, and Young Playwrights Festival.
  - Professional papers and production files, circa 1976-1986; 21 (Box 24)
    Includes A Chorus Line, Dreamgirls, Anything Goes, Seesaw, Ballroom, and Our Father.
  - Professional papers, circa 1975-1983; 46 (Box 25)
  - Professional papers, 1975-1984; 33 (Box 26)
    Primarily contains files on labor relations.
  - Professional papers, 1978-1985; 40 (Box 27)
    Primarily contains files on the property at 890 Broadway.
  - Professional papers, circa 1977-1985; 52 (Box 28)
  - Professional papers, personal papers, and production files, 1973-1984; 34 (Box 29)
  - Professional papers and production files, circa 1978-1985; 41 (Box 30)
    Includes Children's Crusade, Chess, Sweatshop, and Dreamgirls.
  - Scripts, undated; 6 (Box 31)
  - Personal papers, 1983-1985, undated; 16 (Box 31)
  - Personal papers and professional papers, 1978-1986; 38 (Box 32)
  - Financial records, 1977-1987; 18 (Box 33)
  - Financial and business records, 1977-1986; 30 (Box 34)
    Includes records for Quadrille Productions and Plum Productions.
  - Personal papers, circa 1972-1986; 32 (Box 35)
    Primarily personal correspondence.
  - Diaries and daily calendars, 1972-1982; 14 (Box 36)
  - Diaries and daily calendars and other personal papers, 1978-1985; 10 (Box 37)
  - Photographs, circa 1950-1986; 26 (Box 38)
    Includes photographs of A Chorus Line, Follies, A Joyful Noise, Seesaw and Michael Bennett.
  - Scrapbooks, circa 1976-1986
  - Posters, circa 1973-1986
- Awards and Objects, 1970-1989; Series II; 12.42 linear feet (13 boxes)
  Not arranged in any particular order.
  Series II contains awards and objects owned by Michael Bennett, relating to his theatre career. Included are Tony Award nominations and trophies, Drama Desk awards, Los Angeles Drama Critics awards, and other awards. The series also includes objects presented to Bennett in recognition of his role in various Broadway productions as well as a few photograph albums relating to Broadway productions.
  - Tony Award nomination certificates, 1967-1982; 14 (Box 39)
  - Tony Award nomination certificates, 1976-1980; 4 (Box 40)
  - Framed photographs, awards and nomiations, 1970-1983, undated; 8 (Box 40)
  - Framed items, undated
    Includes Pulizter Prize for A Chorus Line.
  - Framed photographs, undated
  - Awards, 1976-1979
  - Tony Award nomination certificates, 1969-1979; 8 (Box 41)
  - Photograph albums, A Chorus Line, binder, 1983, undated; 5 (Box 41)
  - Tony Award trophies, 1972-1983; 7 (Box 42)
  - Mr. Abbott award for a lifetime achievement in theater, awarded to Bennett posthumously, 1989 Nov 13 (Box 43)
  - Broadway Show League Division Championship, trophy awarded to A Chorus Line team, 1986 (Box 44)
  - Drama Desk Awards, undated; 2 (Box 44)
  - Drama Educators of America award, 1982 (Box 44)
  - Astaire Award presented to Bennett for A Chorus Line, 1982 (Box 45)
  - NAACP award presented to Bennett for Dreamgirls, 1983 (Box 46)
  - Star Award Theatre Collection Council Museum of the City of New York, undated (Box 47)
  - Harkness dance award, 1979 (Box 48)
  - Photograph of Bob Avian, Harold Prince, and Bennett at rehearsal of Company, undated (Box 49)
  - Los Angeles Drama Critics Circle Awards, 1974-1977; 3 (Box 49)
  - Musical Theatre Society of Emerson College Award, 1980 May (Box 49)
  - Frame presented to Bennett by Frederick Brisson for Coco, undated (Box 50)
  - Alarm clock presented to Bennett by Katherine Hepburn for Coco, undated (Box 50)
  - Goblet presented for The Good Doctor, undated (Box 50)
  - Box presented to Bennett by Marvin Schulman (or possibly Marvin Hamlisch), undated (Box 50)
  - Cigarette box given to Bennett by Frederick Brissou for Twigs, undated (Box 50)
  - Cigarette box presented to Bennett by David Geffen for opening of Dreamgirls, undated (Box 50)
  - Box presented to Bennett by David Merrick for Promises, Promises, undated (Box 50)
  - Cup presented to Bennett for Ballroom, undated (Box 50)
  - Engraved cigarette case, undated (Box 50)
  - Lifetime pass to all Shubert Theatres presented to Bennett by the Shubert Organization for A Chorus Line, undated (Box 50)
  - Miniature box presented to Bennett by George Furth for Twigs, undated (Box 50)
  - Box presented to Bennett for A Chorus Line by James Kirkwood, undated (Box 50)
  - Miniature baseball cap, undated (Box 50)
  - Miniature Revere bowl presented to Bennett for concert version of Follies, 1985 (Box 50)
  - Decorative box, undated (Box 50)
  - Picture frame presented to Bennett for God's Favorite, undated (Box 50)
  - Cigarette case presented to M.B. by Bernard and Betty Jacobs and Gerald and Pat Schoenfeld of the Shubert Organization for Ballroom, undated (Box 50)
  - Whistle presented to M.B. for Company, undated (Box 50)
  - Tray presented to M.B. by Ken Howard for Seesaw, undated (Box 50)
  - Glass high-heeled shoe, undated (Box 51)
  - Revere bowl presented to Bennett by the cast of Ballroom, undated (Box 51)
  - Gold and platinum records for A Chorus Line, undated
  - Drama Critics Circle Award for A Chorus Line, 1975
  - Framed Follies poster, undated
  - Engraved silver plates, undated
- Audiovisual Material, 1966-circa 1986; Series III; 5 linear feet (5 boxes)
  Series III contains audiovisual materials recording live performances on stage and television, as well as commercial recordings of soundtracks and movie productions.
  Organized by format.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 52-55, 68-69 (audio and video tapes): Restricted Fragile Material. Access to original audio and video tapes is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Contact Access Services for further information.
  - Audiocassettes, circa 1973-1986; 165; Includes 3 empty cassette cases
    - First Day, [1980?] June18; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970534)
    - First Day, tape #1, [1980?] June 18; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970542)
    - "A Chorus Line" - The Movie, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970559)
    - "Smile", Act I, 1986 October 17; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970575)
    - "Smile", Act II, 1986 October 17; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970567)
    - "Chess", Part I, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970583)
    - "Chess", sides E and F, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970591)
    - "Chess", Part I, 1984; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970609)
    - "Chess", Part II, 1984; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970617)
    - "Chess", Part II, 1984; 1 (Box 52)
      This is a duplicate of a commercial audiocassette. It has not been digitized.
    - "Chess", sides A-D, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970633)
    - "Evita", studio recording, part 2, 1976; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970625)
    - "Children's Crusade", Act, 1st Children's Theatre, 1983 May 1; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970641)
    - "A Children's Crusade", 1987 May; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970674)
    - "Children's Crusade", tape 1, Act I and II, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970682)
    - "Jungle", 4 songs - Act I, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970658)
      A list of contents are included.
      Ain't I Somethin'
      Come Save Me
      Gentlemen Out on a Spree
      Only Steal from Thieves
      Applause / Knockers
      Charge It to A.R.
      I Was Made for Champagne
      The Music Went Out of My Life
      Cut of the Cards
      To Overcome Passion
      Man Nobody Could Love
      Don't Say It's Over
      All I Wanted was the Dream
    - "Don't Make Waves", Menken/Brown, 1980; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970666)
    - P.G. Ref Tape - End Face Your Way..., #3, 1981 March 26; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970716)
      Contents listed on this audiocassette include "Cadillac Car", "Sounds to Heart", and "Move Beat".
    - P. G. Ref Tape - "Cadilliac" aria cont. / P. 11-22 with today's changes, "I Meant You No Harm", "Cad"/"Movin", #4, 1981 March 26; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970724)
    - P.G. - "Cadillac"/"Movin", P. 1-20, Baby Aria, #5, March 26; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970690)
    - P.G. Ref Tape - "Cad"/"Movin", P. 19, review pp 13-19 / P. 21, #6, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970708)
    - P.G. Tape #10, 1981 January 27; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970799)
      A list of contents with this audiocassette includes: "Steppin' to the Bad Side", "I Am Somebody", and new "Party, Party".
    - P.G. Ref. Tape #11 - "Party, Party", P. 32, 1981 January 27; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970807)
    - P.G. Ref. Tape #12 - walk through Act I, new "Bad Side" cleanup, p. 25, 26 work, "Movin" on p. 28, aria - new section, baby aria, 1981 March 30; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970815)
    - P.G. Ref Tape #13 - "We Are a Family", Curtis/Deena, p. 2-16, 16a, "One More Pic", Deena/Curtis [p.] 2-15, 16a, p. 2-19 - "I Found You", 1981 March 30; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970823)
    - P.G. Ref. Tape #14 - clean, "Baby Aria"..."More Than You", "I Am Somebody", "Wonderful", 1981 March 31; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970831)
    - P.G. Ref Tape #15 - "Ladies"/"Movin'" reps p. 43A...p. 16B through Jimmy fired, 1981 March 31; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970849)
    - P.G. #16 - "Eppie" / "CC", "One Night Only", p.2-30 through 32, 1981 March 31; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970856)
    - P.G. Ref. Tape #17 - p. 44 "Heavy into Vegas", run through with changes is last thing on this side, "Heavy" aria, new rhythm-new aria, 1981 April 2; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970864)
    - P.G. Tape #18 - p. 43A "Sand" Act I ("Heavy" new) (without "Effie") / Aria fixed, 43A-58 (no "Michelle" song), end Act I, 1981 April 2; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970872)
    - Act II opening and aria, August 19; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970732)
    - DG 1st SF Preview / Curran, tape I, 1983 December 10; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970740)
    - Aria P. 7 - Lornnell/Jimmy/Curtis (new), dance music, 1981 January 23; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970757)
    - "Walkin Down the Street", "Dance Dance Dance", "When I First Saw You"..."Fake Your Way to Top", discussion about stealing and recording songs, 1981 February 2; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970765)
    - Dreamgirls - Radio Promo Spots (#1-3, NY; #4, LA), undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970773)
    - NY Dreamgirls spots: 1) overlap 2) "One Night Only" 3) DeeJays - "Steppin" 4) DeeJays - "Fake Your Way", undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970781)
    - LA Dreamgirls spots: 1) overlap 2) "One Night Only" 3) Jennifer in LA 4) DeeJays - "Steppin'" 5) DeeJays - "Fake Your Way", undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970880)
    - "Dream Girl", undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970906)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970898)
    - Aude songs, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970914)
    - "Ballroom" - 6 songs, 1978 September 30; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970922)
    - David Foster - M.B. and M.P. (important #9 tape!), undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970930)
    - "Ballroom" - 6 songs, 1978 September 30; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970948)
    - MB / Public Radio Interview, aired NYC, 1986 January 10; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970955)
    - "Ballroom", undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970963)
      A list of contents with this audiocassette is included.
      1. A Song for Dancing
      2. Dreams
      3. More of the Same
      4. I've Been Waiting All My Life
    - "Ballroom", 6 songs, 1978 September 30; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970971)
    - M.B. Notes, 1983 September 29; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970989)
    - London #2, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109970997)
    - Thomashefsky / Bennett - cont. reminiscing how I met Trish, ends at 1st trip to Europe, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971003)
    - MB / talks through new 2nd act, 1981 March 23; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971011)
    - "Baby"- Original Broadway Cast, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971029)
      A list of contents is included with this audiocassette.
      Opening - We Start Today
      What Could Be Better
      The Plaza Song
      Baby, Baby, Baby
      I Want It All
      At Night She Comes Home
      Fatherhood Blues
      Romance I Chose Right
      The Story Goes On
      The Ladies Singing Their Song
      Patterns
      Romance II
      Easier to Love
      Romance III
      Two People in Love
      With You
      And What if We had Loved...
      The Birth - Finale
    - Thomashefsky / Bennett - Concerns, conversations over period of work days/nights, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971037)
    - Sc. 3, Sc. 4, 1981 February 12; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971045)
    - Michael, Slim - Menage (2), September 5; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971052)
    - Boston, Act 1, 1974 July 8; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971060)
    - "Dream Girl", undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971078)
    - "Dream Girl", undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971086)
    - London #1, March 24; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971094)
      Annotation on this audiocassette reads: To M - "A Chorus Line", Drory Lane March 24th, British Company - with love xx.
    - disc of young boy - 2, September 15; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971102)
    - S. DiFiglia - "Odd Couple", undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971110)
    - Thurs. Sept 11 - 3 (4) les., September 11; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971128)
    - Thomashefsky / Bennett - Reminiscing, past living experiences in Europe, early 70s, return to states to when I met Trish, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971136)
    - "Ballroom" opening, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971144)
    - "Follies" I and II, 1985 June 28; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971151)
    - MB Personal (SF/DMck), 1976; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971169)
    - "Childhood" - background, personal, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971177)
    - Michael - Menage (1), September 5; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971193)
    - Michael - Menage (3), September 8; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971185)
    - Menage (4), September 4; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971201)
    - Wed. Sept. 9 (1), September 9; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971219)
    - Tues. Sept. 8 - Michael - menage (1), Michael all the roles, September 8; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971227)
    - Wed. Sept. 9 (2), scenes with food menage, coffee [?], September 9; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971235)
    - Act 1, 1981 April 9; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971243)
    - "Dream Girl", undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971250)
    - "Ballroom", orch reading-2, 1978 October 18; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971268)
    - Thurs. Sept. 11 (2) (notes are #1 of today), September 11; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971276)
    - Workshop #3 Tapes: #1 Aria - "Dance, Dance, Dance" through Effie entrance, "Walking Down the Street", "What Color Are You Curtis", 1981 January 14; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971284)
    - Workshop #3 Tapes: #2 Aria, Act II, Aria (without Effie), 1981 January 20; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971292)
    - Workshop #3 Tapes: #3 Act II scenes 3, 4, 5 / Act II Aria (opening), 1981 January 19; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971300)
    - Workshop #3 Tapes: #6 Aria, Henry singing new Effie / "This Ain't No Party", "Long Tim", Henry singing new Michelle into [?], 1981 January 29-30; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971367)
    - Workshop #3 Tapes: #10 Ms. Chocolata, Deena discussion, Take 1, 2, Washington, 1981 February 5; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971383)
    - Workshop #3 Tapes: #11 Medley Aria, test scene-aria to Effie to "Effie/cc", 1981 February 5; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971391)
    - Chorus-session, "Ballroom" anecdotes, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971318)
    - Act I, 1981 April 10; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971326)
    - Act II, 1981 April 10; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971334)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971342)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971359)
    - New sc. 7, Act 1 rehash, 1981 February 2-3; 1 (Box 52, Item barcode 39002109971375)
    - Stravinsky - Petroughka / Finale and Excerpts, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971409)
    - Bob Crewe, Generation, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971417)
    - Bad News - Funny Face, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971425)
    - DG - 1st SF Preview / Curran, 1983 December 10; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971433)
    - Michael - Menage (2) - I Think a Day Either Way, September 8; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971441)
    - Dreamgirls, Original Broadway Cast Album, 1982; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971458)
    - "One and Only" Matinee, Act II, 1983 April 13; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971466)
    - "Say Amen, Somebody", 1983; 1 (Box 53)
      This is a commercial audiocassette. It has not been digitized.
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971474)
    - Gallery, "The Trunk Reel", III, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971482)
    - Gallery, "The Trunk Reel", III, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971516)
    - Gallery, "The Trunk Reel", III, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002109971524)